## Aleksandre Bugadze

Georgia, Tbilisi

+995 599 913 158

leksobugadze@gmail.com

aleksandrebugadze.com

## About me

Hi, my name is Aleksandre. I'm a Software Engineer with 2+ years of experience in developing responsive web applications with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, NextJS, TypeScript, Java, Spring boot, Node.js, Express.js, TailwindCSS, PostgreSQL and MongoDB.

# Work Experience

- Web Administrator, OnMarket (Part-Time), Tbilisi (from July 2022 to December 2022)
   During my employment at OnMarket as Web Administrator, I was responsible for making sure that product that was in our database was displayed on website with proper formatting and accurate specifications.
- Cashier/Consultant, 2Nabiji (Part-Time), Tbilisi (from April 2022 to October 2022)
   As a Cashier/Consultant at 2Nabiji I was responsible for customer service and managing expiration dates of products.

# Education

• Computer Science, Tbilisi State University (from September 2023 – Present)
At Tbilisi State University as a computer science student, I am currently learning about core concepts of programming, data bases, algorithms, linear algebra and etc.

### **Technical Skills**

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- TypeScript
- TailwindCSS
- NextJS

- NodeJS
- ExpressJS
- Java
- Spring boot
- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB

# **Personal Projects**

## Find Location App

This is a full-stack application that utilizes two APIs to provide location-based functionality. The first is an IP Geolocation API, which retrieves geographical information based on an IP address, email, or domain. The second is Leaflet.js, a JavaScript library used to render interactive maps. The application combines these technologies to display the retrieved location data visually on a map, offering a dynamic and user-friendly interface. It was coded using TypeScript, React, TailwindCSS, Java and Spring boot.

#### <u>Live Demo</u> | Source Code

#### To-Do List

To-Do List Web App is developed using React.js and Tailwind CSS for the front end and Node.js and Express.js for the back end. It uses a MongoDB database to store and manage user accounts and tasks in an efficient manner.

#### <u>Live Demo</u> | <u>Source Code</u>

#### **WEATHER APP**

Weather App is coded using JavaScript, HTML, and CSS for the front-end and Node.js and Express.js for the back end. It incorporates the OpenWeather API to get live weather data so that users can look for real-time weather by city.

# <u>Live Demo</u> | <u>Source Code</u>

## **ROGUE CUBE**

Rogue Cube is a tiny, rogue-like, isometric grid-based game constructed with JavaScript, HTML, and CSS. It includes features such as turn-based movement and a modular structure which illustrates fundamental game development principles like state management, user input, and dynamic rendering in a web browser.

<u>Live Demo</u> | <u>Source Code</u>

### OTHER...

There are other smaller projects I've created, which you can view on my Git Hub.